tineye.com 2014-06-28

# Privacy Policy - TinEye

### TinEye Privacy Policy

**Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or provide your personal information to third parties for any purpose without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which TinEye uses and protects your personal information.**

Your use of our website or registration to use any of our services will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use our services or access our site.

#### Information we collect.

Information TinEye collects generally falls into two categories: (1) information you provide us, which is gathered with your specific knowledge and consent, for example when you register to use our services and are asked to provide information such as your email address, your name, phone number, billing address and/or credit information, and (2) information collected through the use of technology, which includes general tracking information collected as you use TinEye and the TinEye Services. This information includes:  
**Cookies:** Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We use them to recognize you. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features of our site or services.  
**Device Information:** We may collect information about the type of computer (hardware and operating system version) or mobile device you are using to access our services.  
**Log files:** When you use our services, we may automatically log certain information about your use of the services. This information may include how you use the service, your internet protocol address, your search query, the date and time of your query and referrer URL.

#### How we use the information collected.

TinEye uses the collected information to improve our products and services, for billing, identification and authentication purposes, to provide support, to troubleshoot and to respond to your inquiries. TinEye does not however share, transmit or provide your personal information to any third party unless you provide explicit consent to do so, or when it is necessary to:  
\- enforce applicable terms of service.  
\- comply with any applicable law or regulations or cooperate with official investigations.  
\- protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of TinEye, our users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

If TinEye is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### Security

We use a range of security measures both procedural and technical to safeguard and protect your personal information against unauthorized access, theft and loss.

#### Accessing and modifying your personal information

If you registered to use the TinEye services, we provide you with tools to access, modify or delete your personal information. You can do this at any time by going to your account profile.

#### Changes

TinEye may amend or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page or if the changes are significant by placing a prominent notice on our site. You retain the right to access, amend, correct or delete your personal information where it is inaccurate at any time. To do so, please contact [support@tineye.com](mailto:support@tineye.com).

#### Contact

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

TinEye  
223 Queen Street East  
Toronto, ON M5A 1S2  
Canada  
Attention: Privacy Policy

Updated April 2012.
